Guide to the Richard Neville Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
Richard Neville papers
1742-2011
1942-2011
GEN MSS 862
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
28.65
(68 boxes) + 1 art, 10 broadside, 2 record album storage, 1 roll
The collection consists of correspondence, writings, notebooks, scrapbooks, photographs, printed materials, artwork, audiovisual materials, and digital media by or related to Richard Neville. The papers document Neville's career as a writer and counterculture leader, especially his work on the Sydney and London versions of the underground magazine Oz. Scrapbooks, correspondence, transcripts, writings, and other papers document Neville's obscenity trials in Australia and England and later dramatizations of the trials. Writings also document Neville's later work for publications such as Rolling Stone. Photographs and papers document Neville's family and childhood in Australia. The collection also includes artwork and other papers relating to Oz art director Martin Sharp.
Neville, Richard, 1941-2016
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Purchased from Richard Neville on the James Marshall and Marie-Louise Osborn Collection Fund, 2011.
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Boxes 68, 69, 72, and 73 (audiovisual materials): Restricted fragile material. Reference copies may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
Box 70 (digital media): Restricted fragile material. Access copies of digital files may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
Box 71: Restricted until 2042. For further information consult the appropriate curator.
Richard Clive Neville (1941-2016)
Richard Clive Neville, an Australian author associated with the counterculture movement of the 1960s and 1970s, was born in Sydney on December 15, 1941. He co-published Oz magazine, an underground magazine that was the subject of high-profile obscenity trials in Australia and the United Kingdom. Neville died on September 4, 2016, in Byron Bay, Australia.
Scope and Contents
The collection consists of correspondence, writings, notebooks, scrapbooks, photographs, printed materials, artwork, audiovisual materials, and digital media by or related to Richard Neville. The papers document Neville's career as a writer and counterculture leader, especially his work on the Sydney and London versions of the underground magazine Oz. Scrapbooks, correspondence, transcripts, writings, and other papers document Neville's obscenity trials in Australia and England and later dramatizations of the trials. Writings also document Neville's later work for publications such as Rolling Stone. Photographs and papers document Neville's family and childhood in Australia. The collection also includes artwork and other papers relating to Oz art director Martin Sharp.
Arrangement
Organized into four series: I. Papers, 1742-2011. II. Audiovisual materials, 1967-1968. III. Electronic media. IV. Restricted Papers.
Oz (Sydney, N.S.W.); Oz (London, England); Authors, Australian -- 20th Century -- Archives; Counterculture -- 20th Century; Trials (Obscenity) -- England -- London; Underground press publications -- Australia -- New South Wales -- Sydney; Underground press publications -- England -- London; Audiovisual materials; Born digital; Photographs; Authors -- Australia -- 20th Century; Neville, Richard, 1941-2016; Sharp, Martin, 1942-2013
- Papers, 1742-2011; Series I; 25.6; (62 boxes) + 1 art, 10 broadside, 1 roll
  Arrangement
  Organized roughly in the arrangement in which it was received.
  - Photograph album, 1900s-1940s (Box 1)
    Scope and Contents
    Inscribed "To Richard with best wishes from Betty Cowper, 15 Dec. '41", which is Richard Neville's birthday. This album holds the earliest Neville family images.
  - Card album with photographs, 1928-1934 (Box 1)
    Records the early years of Richard Neville's parents.
  - Photograph album, 1930s (Box 1)
    Contains childhood snapshots of Josie and Jill Neville.
  - Photograph album, 1940s-1950s (Box 1)
  - Early family papers, 1940s-1960s
    - Intermediate certificate - New South Wales Department of Education, 1957 (Box 1)
    - Leaving certificate - Knox Grammar School, 1959 (Box 1)
    - Letters to family, 1950s (Box 1)
      Also contains a grade school photograph of Richard Neville.
    - Birth and baptismal certificate - New South Wales, 1940s-1960s (Box 1)
    - University bandolier (Box 1)
  - Insurance policy, 1958 (Box 1)
    Contains an insurance policy for Richard Neville's pump action Browning.
  - Correspondence, 1963-1966 (Box 1)
    Regarding Richard Neville's earliest journalism, script-writing and consultancy.
  - Tharunka letterhead (Box 1)
  - Earliest address book (Box 1)
  - Papers relating to tax, income, banking, etc., 1950s-1970s (Box 1)
  - Press cuttings, 1960s (Box 2 (Oversize))
    Contains press cuttings collected by Richard Neville's father, Colonel Clive Neville.
  - Student publications, 1960s (Box 1)
    Contains Tharunka spoofs, Noise, and Sorbent Substitute.
  - Libertarian, No. 1, 1957 (Box 1)
    Published by the Libertarian Society at Sydney University.
  - ABC of Anarchism, by Alexander Berkman, 1945 (Box 1)
  - "The Notebook that launched Oz, Summer, 1963" (Box 1)
  - "Confessions and Impressions in print" - scrapbook, 1960s (Box 1)
  - Printer's block for Oz No. 6, 1963 February (Box 1)
  - Court documents and letters relating to Oz, 1960s (Box 1)
  - Transcripts of the Australian Oz court cases (Box 1)
    Contains annotated transcripts of both the first and subsequent successful appeals.
  - Early passport photograph, 1960s (Box 1)
  - Richard Neville postcard, 1960s (Box 1)
    Shows Richard Neville and an old woman dancing in the street after Neville's successful appeal.
  - "Pot Trail Letters", 1962-1968 (Box 3 (Oversize))
  - "Hippie Trail" - pink document folder (Box 4)
  - Correspondence - black Eastlight folder, 1967-1969 (Box 5 (Oversize))
  - Oz letter head - sample (Box 4)
  - Ian Stocks' obituary of Aggy Read, 1998 (Box 4)
  - Seating plan for the Honi Soit dinner, 1962 (Box 4)
    Contains press cuttings, Martin Sharp's artwork reproduced and pasted up for the UNSW Alumni papers, with a Richard Neville feature copy.
  - "Flowerchild" negative, circa 1967 (Box 4)
    From Oz 5, June 1967, Special Surprise issue.
  - "The Pornography of Violence", 1960s (Box 3 (Oversize))
    Artwork for Oz No. 10.
  - Drug law reform petition circulated by Oz, 1960s (Box 3 (Oversize))
  - Oz / Ink mailing list, 1960s (Box 4)
  - Oz press book cuttings - handbills and related papers (Box 3 (Oversize))
    Contains mostly reproductions of late 1960s, early1970s material.
  - David Leitch funeral service, 2004 (Box 4)
  - Drawing paper block containing clippings with Oz label - "OZ FILES: Students and Education. United States", circa 1969 (Box 6 (Oversize))
  - Drawing paper block containing clippings with Oz label - "OZ FILES: Personalities, General and Personal Interests e.g. Book Reviews, Articles, Arts, Plays, Drama, etc.", circa 1969 (Box 6 (Oversize))
  - Drawing paper block containing clippings with Oz label - "OZ FILES: America: General", circa 1969 (Box 7 (Oversize))
  - Drawing paper block containing clippings with Oz label - "OZ FILES: POP volume I from Jan 69 - Aug 69", circa 1969 (Box 7 (Oversize))
  - Drawing paper block containing clippings with Oz label - "OZ FILES: UK: GENERAL", circa 1969 (Box 8 (Oversize))
  - Drawing paper block containing clippings with Oz label - "OZ FILES: Students and General information on European and other countries. France, Italy, Germany, etc. 1969, Random Order", circa 1969 (Box 8 (Oversize))
  - Drawing paper block containing clippings, circa 1971 (Box 8 (Oversize))
    Contains photocopy of a caricature of Richard Neville.
  - Drawing paper block containing clippings - "Rubin and Frost 1970", circa 1970 (Box 8 (Oversize))
  - "Richard Neville in Print 1970" (Box 8 (Oversize))
  - Oz stickers and subscribers information (Box 4)
  - Oz communication with printers (Box 9 (Oversize))
    Includes copies of correspondence with NRPCO, Thomas Newman, Unity Printers and London, Caledonian.
  - Miscellaneous news cuttings, circa 1970 (Box 9 (Oversize))
  - Play Power, by Richard Neville, circa 1970; 2 (Box 4)
    Contains Richard Neville's annotated copy of Play Power, in preparation for the US edition. Includes folded Headopoloy game, with a scan of Richard Neville's letter agreeing to an American "translation", and a color transparency of the Paladin cover art.
  - Research scrapbook - Play Power, circa 1970 (Box 4)
  - Notebook - pre-Play Power notes, circa 1970 (Box 4)
  - Notebook - Play Power (Box 10)
    Contains early notes for an outline of Play Power.
  - Notebook / Press Book - Play Power, circa 1970 (Box 10)
    Contains press cuttings and typescript quotes from book reviews.
  - BitMan No. 3, 1968 (Box 10)
    Also contains gathered returns of a questionnaire sent out to the Underground Press.
  - FREEk press Friendz, circa 1970 (Box 10)
    Contains all issues of FREEk, which was published at the Isle of Wight Festival. Also contains a black and white photograph, and payment slip.
  - Spare Rib outline and questionnaire (Box 10)
  - UPS New Service - newsletter, circa 1972 (Box 10)
    Contains a lead story by Richard Neville, "News from Miami". Also contains photograph.
  - Rychard Carrington's "Cultural and Ideological Challenges of the London Underground Movement 1965-1971", 2001-2002; 3 (Box 10)
    Richard Neville is mentioned throughout, particularly within Chapter Two. Also contains a conference programme, "The Permissive Society and it's Enemies", from the 15th Summer Conference of the Institute of Contemporary British History, July 9-11, 2001, and a copy of Rychard Carrington's paper "The Ludic Liberalism of Richard Neville".
  - The Right to be Greedy: Thesis on the Practical Necessity of Demanding Everything, circa 1974 (Box 10)
  - The Society of the Spectacle, by Guy Debord, 1970; 1977 (Box 10)
    Contains two copies.
  - Correspondence - binder, 1970-1971 (Box 11 (Oversize))
  - "Economist" diary, 1970 (Box 10)
  - "Letts" desk diary, 1971 (Box 10)
  - "Leathersmith" engagement book, 1972 (Box 10)
  - "Alwych" index address book, 1972 (Box 10)
    Used during United States travels, circa 1972.
  - "Economist" diary, 1973 (Box 10)
  - "Letts" desk diary, 1972 (Box 12)
  - Little Red Schoolbook, by Søren Hansen and Jesper Jensen, 1971 (Box 12)
  - Nasty Tales No. 1, 1971 (Box 12)
  - Viv Berger's Swansong of Love (Box 12)
  - Trials of Oz - draft, circa 1987 (Box 12)
    Contains a photocopy draft of Van Wolf's treatment of Geoffrey Robertson's dramatization.
  - Trials of Oz - draft (Box 12)
    Contains a photocopy draft, with some original notes of Geoffrey Robertson's dramatization.
  - Trial of Oz - playbill magazine, 1972 (Box 12)
    Anderson Theatre: Playbill Magazine, Volume 9, December 1972, Issue 12. This is also the program for the New York production. Directed by Jim Sharman.
  - "Hippie Daze" - film script (Box 12)
    Contains a dramatic adaptation of the Oz Trial.
  - Oz Trial - BBC radio feature, circa 1990 (Box 12)
    Contains a photocopy transcript of the BBC radio feature.
  - Oz Trial - synopsis and introduction to proposed book, circa 1970s (Box 12)
    Contains two typescripts.
  - Kestrel no. 556: Youth Liberation Musical based on the Oz Trial, circa 1970s (Box 12)
    By Adrian Mitchell. Produced by Clive Goodwin. Directed by Maurice Hatton.
  - Dramatic adaptation of the Chicago 8 trial - thermal copy, circa 1986; 2 (Box 12)
  - Yellow Spicers commerce folder (Box 12)
    Contains discarded typescript drafts in revision for an early and abandoned autobiographical work dealing with the Oz years.
  - Oz Schoolkids issue, circa 1971 (Box 12)
    Also contains clippings, specifically: The Times, 6 November 1971, and a typed handbill for the Royal Shakespeare Company's "The Oz Trial".
  - Richard Neville's letter from Wandsworth Prison, circa 1972 (Box 12)
    Also contains Richard Neville's prison notebook, Obscene Courtroom Dramas invitation, Backlash Oz Appeal handbill, Oz Obscenity Trial procession handbill, Presenting The Oz Obscenity Trial, Hate Mail, Oz Obscenity Trial stickers, and Ozjets d'Art - Clytie Jessup fundraising catalogue.
  - "Oz Trial Court Docs", circa 1972 (Box 12)
    Contains: medical reports; a probation officer's report; "Social Enquiry" reports; Richard Neville's statement to the court; a letter from the publisher F. Warburg declining to give evidence; signed witness letters; two summonses regarding Oz 28 "Schoolkids Issue"; a typescript of Richard Neville's letter to his family regarding Oz 28; a marked up photocopy of Richard Neville's opening at the appeal; reflective "opinion" by Geoffrey Robertson on Richard Neville's 1972 conviction for possession of marijuana; marked up legal papers from the firm of Offenbach & Co. concerning legal representation and court transcript of matters involving Richard Neville, Oz and prohibited substances; profile of Judge Argyle; US Embassy letter regarding visa; Document of Identity; and Immigration act documents and cuttings.
  - "Louise" - folder (Box 12)
    Contains notes to John Mortimer, as well as typescript notes for the appeal. Also contains notes regarding Fatty Arbuckle, notes regarding Judge Argyle's comments in court, and extensive strategy notes for witness testimony and cross examination.
  - Richard Neville's Oz Trial notebook, London, circa 1971 (Box 12)
  - Trial transcript, circa 1971; 9 (Box 13)
    Contains eight bundles of trial transcripts which are marked up in preparation of the appeal by Geoffrey Robertson and John Mortimer.
  - D.V. Illingworth's "The Oz Obscenity Trial - A Summing Up" - stage adaptation (Box 14)
  - Andrew Fisher's Oz scrapbook (Box 14)
    Contains comprehensive press cuttings, photographs and ephemera, as well as correspondence between Richard Neville and Andrew Fisher and material for and from a recent London celebration of Fisher's life.
  - Anarchy conference papers, 1975 (Box 14)
  - Andrew Fisher's "A Taste of Oz" - diary, 1971 December (Box 14)
  - Oz Trial T-shirt, 1971; 2 (Box 14)
    Originally purchased by a United Kingdom fan, it features "HoneyBunch" Kaminski, who is a cartoon character created by Robert Crumb and dubbed Jail Bait of the Month. Also included is a note from the former owner.
  - Hippie Hippie Shake, by Richard Neville, 2009 (Box 14)
  - Vote! Abbie and Jerry and Ed Hoffman and Rubin and Sanders, 1972 (Box 14)
  - Lampoon: An Historical Art Trajectory 1970-2010, by Jim Anderson, 2011 (Box 14)
  - Post-Scarcity Anarchism, by Murray Bookchin, 1971 (Box 14)
  - Promise of a Dream: A Memoir of the Sixties, by Sheila Rowbotham - uncorrected proof, 2000 (Box 14)
  - Hello I Love You, by Jeanne Pasle-Green and Jim Haynes, 1974 (Box 14)
  - Lee Heater material (Box 14)
  - Germaine Greer material (Box 14)
  - "Dingology", 3 (Box 14)
    Richard Neville's research files for his Dingo book. Contains notebooks, newspaper cuttings and assorted papers.
  - Green binder (Box 15 (Oversize))
  - "The Daily News - clippings from David" - photocopies, 1972 (Box 15 (Oversize))
  - Sydney's "Beats" - clippings, 1975 February (Box 15 (Oversize))
    Published by the National Times of Sydney in February 1975. Comments on Sydney, Australia's bohemians - "the Push" - and provides an insight into how the group shaped the intellectual life of the whole city.
  - Daily Mirror -Sydney, Australia, 1970 October 2 (Box 15 (Oversize))
    Contains, on page 22, a story relating to the appearance of the Oz editors in a London magistrates court.
  - "Tharunka" - UNSW student newspaper, 1964 February (Box 15 (Oversize))
    Contains the Orientation Week issue, edited by Alex Popov and Michael Robertson. The back page features a full page cartoon by Martin Sharp, "The Gas Lash", which resulted in the arrival of the Vice Squad on campus. The editors were prosecuted for obscenity and later acquitted. Paper also contains a half page add for Oz magazine.
  - "Tharunka" - UNSW student newspaper, copy (Box 15 (Oversize))
    Contains a copy of the September 1964 issue, which covers the prosecution of Sydney Oz magazine and the jail sentences handed out to Richard Neville, Martin Sharp and Richard Walsh.
  - National Times "Rough Radio", 1975 (Box 16)
  - "Ink Records" - empty folder (Box 16)
  - Letters To No One: Diaries, Volumes 1-2, 1971-1974; 2 (Box 17 (Oversize))
  - Quadrant: Three Villages of Phuoc Tuy, 1967 (Box 16)
  - Obscenity, No. 1, 1967 (Box 16)
  - Time: Australia, 1988 January 11 (Box 16)
  - Ad-Lib Reading Guide to Anarchism, by Ross Laird, circa 1973 (Box 16)
  - The Totality for Kids, by Raoul Vaneigem, circa 1966 (Box 16)
  - The Writing on the Wall, by Roger Perry, 1976 (Box 16)
  - The Trials of Oz, by Tony Palmer, 1971 (Box 16)
  - The Politics of Ecstasy, by Timothy Leary, 1970 (Box 16)
  - Martin Sharp material, circa 1966 (Box 18 (Oversize))
    Contains Politics of Ecstasy, color transparencies of Martin Sharp, and The Endless Summer magazine tie-in with Bruce Brown's film (circa 1966), including a comic strip and advertising artwork and layout by Martin Sharp.
  - "Images letters telegrams of Judy Ahern" - folder, 1970s (Box 16)
  - Miscellaneous papers, circa 1965-2007 (Box 16)
    Contains a facsimile copy of a letter on Apple letterhead to "Ian" from Yoko Ono Lennon pointing out incorrect information in an article in BitMan (January 1972). Also contains newspaper cuttings, facsimile copies of letters from Horwitz Publishers, and a copy of Private Eye (August 1971).
  - Andrew Fisher manuscripts, 10 (Box 16)
    Includes "The Sex Collective", a guide to staging a sex party or orgy.
  - "A Taste of Oz", by Andrew Fisher - play (Box 19)
  - Oz badges (Box 19)
    Eleven buttons.
  - Martin Sharp cartoons, 1966 (Box 19)
  - Up Against the Law, Volume 1, No. 1 - newsletter, 1970s (Box 19)
    Contains McKenzie Lawyer's article, which was influential in the Oz trial (see Widgery).
  - Lillian Roxon letter: Do's and Don'ts, circa 1970 (Box 19)
    Pertaining to the promotion of Play Power.
  - "For CIA article - in envelope address forwarded to Jan Wenner at Rolling Stone", 1972 (Box 19)
    Includes typescript of draft.
  - Foolscap Olympic Stripe lecture book (Box 19)
    Contains Richard Neville's notes of reconstructing the development and significant moments in the production of Australian Oz and the London Oz. Oz, Love, Obscenity and Me.
  - Ryman Conran mushroom card document folder (Box 19)
    Contains an annotated typescript draft for a memoir of Oz magazine.
  - Sydney draft - Rolling Stone article, circa 1970 (Box 19)
    Contains an eleven page typescript draft about Sydney, Australia for Rolling Stone magazine, with handwritten amendments and corrections by Richard Neville. Written shortly after his return to Australia.
  - Rolling Stone article - draft, 1972-1973 (Box 19)
    Contains twenty-two pages of a typescript draft for a Rolling Stone magazine article on how Richard Neville found Australia after years abroad.
  - "Pink folder" (Box 19)
    Contains typescript drafts of a film outline by David Elfick, which involved the efforts of Andrew Fisher and Richard Neville.
  - Richard Neville's Australian Security Intelligence Organisation (ASIO) file, circa 2005 (Box 19)
  - Alternative Pink Pages, Sydney Summer '73, 1973 February (Box 19)
  - The Little Green Book: The Facts On Green Bans, 1973 (Box 19)
  - Uni NSW Graduates 1964 - names and addresses, 1994 (Box 19)
  - Card advertising "The Oz 3, Free!" - A history painting by Caroline Coon, 1996 June (Box 19)
  - "At Last" - advertising ephemera - Oz publication INK Ltd., United Kingdom (Box 19)
  - Oz, Love, Obscenity and Me - bound drafts, 1970s (Box 19)
    Forty-four pages in length, this draft ends with "To be continued... for four more years... until the Old Bailey Oz Trial ...and its aftermath..."
  - Ulterior Motives, by Lucienne Joy - uncorrected proof, 2008 (Box 19)
    Based on Lucienne Joy's marriage to Andrew Fisher.
  - Hippie Hippie Shake, by Richard Neville, 2009 (Box 19)
  - Communes in rural Australia, by Margaret Munro-Clark, 1986 (Box 19)
  - The Revolution of Everyday Life, by Raoul Vaneigem, 1979 (Box 19)
  - Energy from Nature, circa 1992 (Box 19)
  - Children's Rights: toward the liberation of the child, by Paul L. Adams, 1971 (Box 19)
  - Ink, No. 9, 1971 June 26 (Box 19)
  - Tibetan hat, circa 1967 (Box 20)
    Feature in London Oz, in 1967.
  - Tibetan hat - photographs, 1967; 2006 (Box 19)
  - Neville family photographs, circa 1900s-1920s (Box 19)
  - Color transparencies and color slides, 2 (Box 21)
    Contains eleven color transparencies from Robert Whitaker's shoot for Oz #17, December 1968, and four color slides.
  - "From Ancient History to 1962" - binder, circa 1962 (Box 22)
  - Binder, 1963-1966 (Box 22)
  - Binder, 1967-1971 (Box 23)
  - Binder, 1972 Part 1, 2 (Box 79)
  - Binder, 1972 Part 2 (Box 80)
  - Binder, 1973-1974 (Box 24)
  - Binder, 1975-1976 (Box 81)
  - Pink binder, Vol. 3, Dec. 74 - Oct. 75, 1974-1975 (Box 82)
  - Binder, Vol. 4, Dec. 75 - July 76 (Aust.), 1975-1976 (Box 82)
  - MacKnight family bible, 1742 (Box 25)
    Contains Richard Neville's maternal family bible, which is approximately 200 years old.
  - MacKnight family book of common prayer, 1760 (Box 25)
    Contains Richard Neville's maternal family book of common prayer, which is approximately 200 years old.
  - Clive Neville's medals and awards, circa 1910s-1940s (Box 26)
    Contains a small Jenny Kee designed box, which holds the medals and awards of Richard Neville's father, Clive Neville.
  - Ink sweater, circa 2007 (Box 27 (Oversize))
    Recreated by Working Title Pictures for the movie Hippie Hippie Shake (2007). It is based on the original.
  - Oz Trial t-shirt, circa 1970 (Box 27 (Oversize))
    An original London Oz Trial t-shirt, featuring Detective Luff, by Felix Dennis.
  - Richard Neville's Jenny Kee Kookaburra cardigan sweater, circa 1970s (Box 28 (Oversize))
  - Photographs of the MacKnight family - album, circa 1890s (Box 29)
    Ornate Victorian album with a brass clasp, which contains photographs of the MacKnight family in Scotland, leading up to their emigration to Australia.
  - "The Castle At Bungan Head" - Ninon Jordan Smith (Box 29)
    Written by Betty Neville's sister, who was an author and illustrator working under the name Ninon MacKnight. Contains manuscript with illustrations.
  - "Anybody can Cook! Sixty Different Dinners" - Betty Neville, 1952 (Box 29)
    Typed recipe sheets.
  - "Newport Summer, Betty's Diary", circa 1925 (Box 29)
    The diary of Betty Neville.
  - Passport and travel documents - Archibald MacKnight, 1920s-1930s (Box 30)
  - Album-scrapbook - Bertha Fanning, 1890s-1900s (Box 30)
    Contains the album of Bertha Fanning, Betty Neville's mother. The label reads: "Concert reviews, Programs, gossip, etc from 1895-1905 including her London tour and her mysterious return to Sydney..." Includes programs, handbills, press notices, reviews, notes, correspondence and confirmations. Also includes an envelope labelled "fragments from a notebook by Berthe McKnight (nee Fanning) recalling her childhood in Newcastle in the 1870s written for her children".
  - Betty Neville's Journalism and Poetry - album, 1920-1940 (Box 30)
    A cloth covered album which contains newspaper clippings.
  - Harold MacKnight scrapbook, 1893-1899 (Box 30)
    A red scrapbook album containing newspaper clippings.
  - Scrapbook - Lucy Lockett, 1950s (Box 30)
    Contains columns published in Country Life by Lucy Lockett, the pen name of Betty Neville.
  - Dalton Thomas Walker Neville - photographs and clippings, circa 1919-1969; 2 (Box 31 (Oversize))